第三亲帜痪Wwww.disanlou.org最新字幕共享平_
W友共享字幕H供翻g交流使用, 禁止用於商I用途
不好意思... Σ黄
I'm sorry... Sorry
中英g/校/rgS 新浪微博：@h球影小笳娴牟皇IN啊
]事 坐那
No, Stay
叫什麽？
What's your name?
安德・嚷
Andrew Neyman.
啄昙？
What year are you?
大壹
I'm... a first year
知道我是l麽
You know who I am?
知道
Yes sir.
所以知道我在找肥
So you know I'm looking for players?
知道
Yes sir.
那怎麽不打了
Then why did you stop playing?
我再接著打了麽
Did I ask you to start playing again?
-不好意思我以..  -我怎麽不打了跟公仔猴似的坐那是什麽意思？
-Ugh, I'm sorry... -I asked you why did you stop playing and your version of an answer was to turn into a wind-up monkey
-Σ黄.. -o我看看基本功
-I'm.. I'm sorry  -Show me your rudiments.
-好的
Yes sir.
p倍u[
Double time swing
p倍 p起
No double time, double it
快c
Faster
Faster!
哎 忘拿外套了
Woopsy-daisy, forgot my jacket.
不要炸~了
No Swedish Fish?
今天不用了
Not today.
xx
Thanks.
-]事吧？ -]事啊
-You ok?  -Yeah
哎 他今天看到我鼓了
Yeah, I don't know. He saw me play today.
然後呢？
And?
可走的路多著呢
You got plenty of options still.
什麽意思 什麽路？
What does that mean? Other options?
就是...
Just.. You know.
@就是人生
It's just life.
等到了我@年o 就不@牛角尖了
You get to be my age, you get perspective.
我就想要@牛角尖
I don't want perspective
抱歉
Sorry.
我不想要葡萄
I don't want raisin in it.
那怎麽不早f
Why didn't you say that?
我@著吃就好了
I just eat around them.
真不懂
I don't understand you.
操@是l啊瑞安
My man Ryan, yo shit!
多久]了
How you feeling man?
嚷那鼓打的太糟心了
Things were hurting with Neyman on the kits.
Hey嚷 周末怎麽影
Hey what's up bro. Had a good weekend?
挺好的 特_心
Yeah real good. Lot of fun.
e理格雷格 他就是嘴v
Hey, don't worry about Greg. He's a dick.
]事
No big deal.
早上好
Good morning everybody.
早 上 好
早上好...
Morning.
嗯 先Billy's Ann 念^起 ]}吧？
Alright. Let's do Billy's Ann, from the top, yes?
1 2 3 走
One Two Three
好了QReese
Alright let's do... Reese
瑞安
Yo Ryan
巴迪.瑞奇
行啦  行啦
Alright alright.
先到@吧Q回核心鼓手
That's enough for that, just back to the core drummer please.
核心肥
Core players, let's go.
@商於季什麽呢
Dude, what've you been practicing?
不介意吧？
May I?
真幼X
Cute.
下面那行 小 78小
Down the line, trumpets, bar 78.
三四
Three Four
好了
Ok, alright.
24小 最後膳拈_始
the bar 24, the end of two.
算了不用了
Maybe not.
211小_始 三四
Let's pick up on 211, Three Four.
壹 三四
Same spot, three four.
行了
Alright.
是首席 砜纯词遣皇强磕蛋鹤到@的
You're in the first chair, let's see if it's just because you are cute.
三四
Three Four.
嗯果然是
Yeah, that's why.
鼓手 碓p倍u[
Drums, let's hear a little double-time swing.
後面那
Behind?
壹
Same thing.
司 之後5小
Bass, five bars down the lead
就@影
Alright.
鼓手 跟我走
Drums, with me.
x了
Thank you Joe
不是 叫他呢
No no no, other drums.
B16房g 明早6c
Room B16, tomorrow morning 6am
et到
Don't be late.
好了大家 念^_始
Alright everybody, from the top.
壹二三
One Two Three
Hey 怎麽影
Hey  How are you?
挺好的 呢
Good, how are you?
好著呢 xx
I'm good, thanks.
老壹套？
The usual?
嗯 我不大了解壹般... 怎麽...
Ugh... Nah, Look I don't know how...
我常在@看到 我X得很漂亮
I see you here a lot, and I think you are... really pretty.
意跟我s麽？
Would you want go out with me... ever?
走_
Please go away.
哦天啊 真Σ黄... Σ黄
Oh my god. I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
我逗呢 逗呢
I'm just messing with you. I'm messing with you.
哦天啊
Oh my god.
Σ黄
I'm sorry.
不能@麽欺人啊
That's actually pretty mean
-Σ黄 叫什麽 -]P系啦
-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.. what's your name? -No big deal.
-哦我叫安德  -哦安德
-Oh I'm Andrew.   -Andrew
我叫妮可
I'm Nicole
很高dJR
Nice to meet you Nicole.
嗯我也是
Nice to meet you too.
所以想s我出去？
So you wanna take me out?
我很想s出去
I'd... love to take you out.
-去哪海 -匹_
-Where you wanna go?  -Pizza.
-匹_ 我喜g匹_ -嗯 我知道壹家很好的匹_店
-Pizza. I like pizza.  -Yeah I know a great pizza place.
好
Cool, well...
我周壹晚上7c下班
I get off at 7 on Monday.
哦是幔
Okay?
-想在@麽 -噢 是是到r候我碚
-You wanna meet here.. -Oh ok, yeah, I will.
好
Great
-嗯 那就7c？
-Ok. Seven o'clock?
-嗯 在@ -7c
-Here   -7pm
-周壹  -嗯 拜
-Monday   -Alright, bye.
是新替a麽
-You are the new alternate?
嗯 我叫安德.嚷
-Yeah, I'm Andrew Neyman.
鼓{到降B{ 排的r候o我翻纷V
-Tune  the set to a B-flat and turn my pages during rehearsal
]}
Sure
抱歉 能o降B{麽？
Excuse me, can you give me a B-flat?
xx
Thank you.
不好意思 再硐驴梢憎幔
Sorry, can you... just one more time?
@鼓架真好
It's a great kit.
逼加o了！
Milk the cunt!
新砹小毛孩
We got a squeaker today people.
嚷 19q
Neyman, 19 years old
可郯
isn't he cute?
好了同I Whiplash
Alright gang, "Whiplash"
翻
Page.
翻！
Page!
巴克 那不是男朋友的u巴 es著高潮
Barker, that is not your boyfriend's dick, do not come early.
93小
Bar 93
五六七走
Five Six and..
停！
Stop!
@很我郁 有人跑{了
Now this one really upsets me. We have an out-of-tone player here.
在我^m前 跑掉的能先站出眵
Before I continue, would that player care to identify himself?
]人？那可能是我耳朵Mx子了
No? Ok, maybe a bug flew in my ear.
115小
五六七走
Five Six and..
嗯 我耳朵很好 是有壹跑{的
No, my ears are fine, we definitely have an out-of-tone player.
不管是l @是最後的C
Whoever it is, this is your last chance.
好吧e^了
And there it went.
要麽是故意跑{拖逢後腿
Now either you are deliberately playing out-of-tone and sabotaging my band
要麽自己都不知道自己跑{了
Or you don't know you are out-of-tone
那恐怕就更糟了
which I'm afraid is even worse.
五六七走
Five Six and..
Bones
五六七走
Five Six and..
就在@
He's here.
eo我f不是 大^鹤
Tell me it's not you, Elmer Fudd.
]P系 吹吧
It's ok. Play.
X得自己跑{了麽
Do you think you are out of tone?
看什... 地上又]巧克力看什麽看
What're you... There's no fucking Mars bar down there, what are you looking at?
E起^ 看著我
Look up here, look at me.
X得 自己跑{了麽
Do you think, you are out of tone?
跑了
Yes.
那他的不吭？！
Then why the fuck didn't you say so?!
梅茨@死胖子在@待太久了
I carried your fat ass for too long Metz
我不能壹每天就知道惦著和套餐不音{的傻逼Я吮荣
I'm not gonna have you cost us a competition because your mind's on a fucking Happy Meal instead of on pitch.
恭喜芸诉d 是四席了
Jackson congratulations, you are fourth chair.
梅茨傻坐著致锬 L蛋啊
Mets why are you still sitting there, get the fuck out!
f明下 梅茨]跑{
For the record, Mets wasn't out of tone
跑{的是 埃Y克森
You were, Ericson
但是他自己都不知道
But he didn't know.
那已蛟懔
And that's bad enough.
休息10分 回磲嵝∶孩上
Alright take 10, when we get back the squeaker is on.
安德
Andrew
爸是搞音返镊
Parents are musicians?
不是
No
做什麽的
What do they do?
我爸是作家
My dad's a writer.
什麽的？
Oh what's he written
主要是老了
I guess he's more of a teacher. Really.
大W？
Oh. College?
彭D中W
Pennington High School.
呢 她是质谗岬
What about your mother? What does she do?
我不知道 很小r候她就x_了
I don't know. She left when I was a baby.
所以家Y]有做音返模
So no musicians in the family?
那就多典吧
Well you just gotta listen to the greats then.
巴迪.瑞奇 .斯
Buddy Rich, Jo Jones
知道查理.帕克成椤按篪B” 是因楫初.斯拿著往他X袋上砸
You know Charlie Parker became Bird because Jo threw a cymbal at his head
懂我意思麽？
See what I'm saying?
PI在於放松
Listen, the key is to just... relax.
e心曲子 e心e人怎麽想
Don't worry about the numbers, don't worry about what the other guys are thinking.
能磉@是有原因的
You are here for a reason.
相信@吧
You believe that right?
嗯
Yeah.
f
Say it.
我能磉@是有原因的
I'm here for a reason.
好
Cool
行了哥 好好玩吧
Alright man, have fun.
同I Whiplash
Alright gang, Whiplash
奏放慢c 嚷
A little under tempo ok? Neyman.
M力就好
Just do your best.
_始
There you go.
五六七走
Five Six and...
睃cЦ械
Let's hear some feels.
巴迪.瑞奇化身啊
We got Buddy Rich here.
有c}
A little trouble there.
17小
Pick it up on 17
五六七走
Five Six and
奏不大
Not quite my tempo.
_始 五六七走
Here we go. Five Six and..
18 _始
Down beat on 18. Here we go.
五六七走
Five Six and...
17小最後4拍
Bar 17 the end of four.
五六七走
Five Six Seven...
奏不大
Not quite my tempo.
]P系慢慢
It's all good, no worries, here we go.
五六七走
Five Six Seven
s了 再
You're rushing. Here we go.
好了？
Ready?
五六七走
Ok. Five Six and...
有c拖
Dragging. Just here.
等我提示
Wait for my cue.
五六七走
Five Six Seven..
s了
Rushing.
五六七走
Five Six and..
拖了
Dragging.
五六七走
Five Six and...
知道我槭谗岢扔椅子麽
Why do you suppose I just hurled a chair at your head, Neyman?
我... 不知道
I.. I don't know.
知道
Sure you do.
奏？
The tempo?
是s了是拖了？
Were you rushing or were you dragging?
我...不知道
I... I don't know.
_始
Start counting.
-五六 -乃拈_始！操 看著我
-Five Six..  -In 4 damnit! Look at me!
壹二三四 壹二三四 壹二三四
One two three four One two three four One two three four
我是s了是拖了？
Now, was I rushing or was I dragging?
不...知道
I don't know.
再
Count again.
壹二三四 壹二三四 壹二三四
One two three four One two three four One two three four
-s了是拖了？  -s了
-Rushing or dragging?  -Rushing.
所以知道^e！
So you do know the difference!
要敢故意o我拖後腿 我他逼的炙
If you deliberately sabotage my band, I'll fuck you like a pig.
所以是要s 是要拖
Now are you a rusher, or are you a dragger
是跟我奏恚浚
Or are you gonna be on my fucking time?!
我跟奏
I'll be on your time.
@上面的什麽
What does that say?
-四分音符等於215 -215o我看看
-Quarter note equals 215   -Count me a 215.
壹二三四 壹二三四
One two three four One two three four
我操他的 x佛什麽r候_始收智障了？
Jesus fucking Christ, I don't know they allow retards into Shaffer.
是想告V我x不懂拍麽？
Am I to understand you cannot read tempo?
他的不BV都不R吧？
Can you even fucking read music?
那是什麽？
What is that?
Yes, what is that?
附c十六分音符
A dotted sixteenth
o我哼下101小
Sing me a measure 101
我操他是清唱F的麽？打鼓啊！
What are you, in a fucking acapella group? Play the goddamn kit!
停！
Stop!
F在o我f
Now answer my question.
是s了是拖了？
Were you rushing, or were you dragging?
f！
Answer!
s了
Rushing.
我靠...
Oh my dear god.
是要玩Io痕麽？
Are you one of those single tear people?
壹看我的就高潮了是麽？
Do I look like a double fucking rainbow to you?
-壹定很y受吧 y受麽？  -不y受
-You must be upset. Are you upset?   -No
不y受 所以根本就不回事？
No. So you just don't give a shit about any of this?
-我回事  -那倒是f啊 y受是他的不y受？
-I do give a shit... -So are you upset, yes or fucking no?
-y受 -y受
-Yes -You are upset.
嗯
Yeah
f出
Say it.
我y受
I'm upset.
大c大家都能到
Say it to the whole band can hear you.
我y受
I'm upset.
大c
Louder.
我y受
I'm upset.
大c！
Louder!
我y受！
I'm upset!
就是]前途]朋友]r值的娘炮逼
You are a worthless friendless faggot-lipped little piece of shit
小r候lF跟e了人扔下和爸走了
Whose mommy left daddy, when she figured out he wasn't Eugene O'neil
L大了跑到老子鼓架上
And who's now weeping and slobbering all over my drum set
跟他小姑娘似的哭鼻子抹眼I
like a fucking nine-year-old girl
我他的再f最後壹次：大c！
So for the final father fucking time... Say it louder!!!
我y受！
I'm upset!!
卡
Carl.
再努力c吧嚷
Start practicing harder Neyman
Whiplash 125小
Whiplash, bar 125.
成年人奏
Big boy tempo
五六七走
Five six and...
“少巡慌力，L大玩uL”
@地方不e
This place is nice.
嗯
Yeah
我喜g他家放的音
I really liked the music that they play.
|西也好吃 不^...
I mean the food is good too, but...
嗯匹_很棒
The pizza is really good.
我醒
When I wake.
什麽？
What?
@首歌的名字
That's the name of the song.
芑.希 1938年7月17
Jacky Hill, July 17th, 1938
鼓手是U勃.埃Y森
Bob Ellis on the drums.
每次在影院看到的r候
You know every time I saw you at the theater
眼睛都死盯著地板
Your eyes were glued to the floor.
是麽？
Really?
我爸f我不知道怎麽跟人做眼神接|
My dad says that I have trouble making eye contact.
我爸也厶粑颐病
My parents like to criticize me too.
小r候我f我下巴很大
When I was growing up my mom said that I had a really big chin.
所以男生都不喜g我
And that's why guys don't like me
-真的？  -是啊
-Really?   -Yeah.
-]有啊 -她f都是我爸咒的
-You don't.  -Well she said my dad curse me with one.
-哪Y有  -有的
-No it's not.   -Yeah it is.
我壹c]X得
I don't... I don't think so at all.
的下巴很... 漂亮
Your chin is very... nice.
很漂亮
Very nice.
了吧哈哈
Your mom sounds insane.
嗯她在我@麽大的r候倒是壹直想演T
Well she did want to be an actress when she was my age.
呢
What about you?
我？
What about me?
F在做什麽呢？
What do you do?
我在福特h姆上W
I go to Fordham.
W什麽呢？
What do you study?
我]有I呢
I don't... have a major yet.
那想W什麽？
...like what do you want to study?
不知道
I don't really know.
不知道呢
I don't know yet.
所以f福特h姆就是S手挑的？
So Fordham was just like a random school?
也不是 我申了壹堆W校 福特h姆了我
No I've applied a bunch of schools, Fordham let me in.
那槭谗崛ブx佛？
Why do you go to Shaffer?
因槟鞘侨最好的音W院
It's the best music school in the country.
那..  福特h姆就是福特h姆而已了
Well Fordham is Fordham.
f我壹c不喜g那
I don't love there to be honest.
-不喜g？  -不喜g
-No?  -No.
不知道... 就X得那的人都不喜g我
I don't know... I guess it's just people there don't like me very much.
我家是利桑那的 我X得他能...
I'm from Arizona, and I think they can...
看出
see it.
嗯我在x佛也是@感X
I kinda feel the same way about people in Shaffer.
我X得他也不... 那麽喜g我
Yeah I don't think they like me too much.
但是我... 我...
But I don't...
我也不大在意
I don't care too much.
我X得人都... 得嘛
I think it's just... it changes.
人了... 也就]事了
You know people change, things work out.
嗯我懂意思
Yeah I know I know I know.
我只是...
I just...
有r候挺想家的
I feel like homesick sometimes.
不知道...
I don't know.
就是挺受不了大家都b自己不想家
Kind pissed me off when people pretend like they are not.
大W麽...
In college, you know.
也可能我真的是唯壹壹想家的吧
Maybe I'm literally the only one, I don't know.
我到F在跟我爸壹起看影呢
I still go to the movies with my dad.
Hey 最近怎麽影
Hey how are you man.
挺好的
Good.
哈哈 @真的是Eva麽？
Is this really Eva?
哇W 上次那麽小呢
Wow, last time I saw you you were very tiny.
_始菲髁
Are you playing an instrument yet?
她上周_始琴了
She started piano last week.
等上了大W
Hey when you are a big college kid
砦逢吧
Will you come and play in my band?
-想去幔 -我的琴吧
-Do you like that? -Would you be my piano player?
太棒了 那就壹言槎啦
Excellent, give me five
-嗯到很高d -到很高d
-Alright, great seeing you. -Great seeing you.
表演完吧 回聊
See you after the show. Alright cheers.
好了小u巴崽子
Listen up cocksuckers!
幼髀槔c
Hurry the fuck up.
拿好纷V
Get your music.
第壹支曲目
奏菲鹘M先出
Rhythm Section out first
坦{ 鼓架的音{直他的K不忍睹
Tanner, the kit is a fucking tonal catastrohpy
soo我弄好了
Get it in tone alright?
奏M和奏部分 45小
Rhythm and soloists, bar 45
奏跟上了
we gonna pick up the tempo there alright?
106小 管 e忘了音{再高半音
Bar 106, brass, do not forget we sharp that knife.
都o我清楚了 林肯中心什麽的都用@霰荣作⒖Q定要l不要l
Everybody remember, Lincoln Center and its ilk use these competitions to decide who they are interested in and who they are not
我Q不允S自己的名
And I am not gonna have my reputation in that department tarnished
г@群痿早泄找不到音比女朋友他逼的小郝楸允稚
by a bunch of fucking limp-dick, sour-note, flattered on their girlfriend's flexible tempo dipshits.
懂？
Got it?
另外 尤金 o我f^
One more thing. Eugene give me that.
如果我再看到有人到y扔V子
If I ever find another one of these lying around again
我他逼的保C我不再@麽客饬
I swear to fucking god I will stop being so polite.
他的有多hL多h不然缌
Get fuck out of my sight before I demolish you.
整理好了 渖吓_
Stage right, in order, now.
我是能看到 小挫逼！
I can still fucking see you, Mini-Me!
幼骺禳c 等什麽呢
Let's go, hurry the fuck up. Let's go.
x佛音W院 音肥逢
Shaffer Conservatory, Studio Band.
o我拿著 下鲅莩鼋o我
Hold onto this for the second set.
...他想在@做I肥
I think he wants a career
但是有弗R卦谶@他焊]法回
But as long as Fletcher is here, Fudd don't have a chance get back in..
o我看下V子
I need to look at the music.
哦在@呢
Oh yeah it's right here.
怎麽不拿在手上？
Why isn't it on you?
V子呢？
Where's the folder?
-逗我呢吧  -我不...
-You're joking right?  -I have no.. No I literally
我真的... 我l誓在@呢
No.. I swear I just had it here two seconds ago
肯定就在附近
It's gotta be around here.
-他X子M屎了麽 -是不是清工^...
-How could you be so fucking stupid? -I don't know, maybe a janitor came bay or something..
-清工？ -嗯
-A janitor?  -Yeah
o我找V子去！他的清工？
-Find the fucking folder! A fucking janitor?!
他完了！操！
You are done! Fuck!
我他完了！操！
I'm done! Fuck!
-找V子去！  -Σ黄
-Find the folder!  -I'm sorry.
坦{!
Tanner!
我操去哪玩了？
Jesus fucking Christ, where have you been??
出了c}..
We have an issue..
哦 F在不是r候
Ok, now is not the time.
我...把V子o了嚷 嚷搞G了
I gave... Neyman the folder and Neyman lost it.
嚷搞G了？
Neyman lost it?
嗯
Yes.
V子是的任
The folder is your fucking responsibility, Tanner
他o嚷致铮
Why would you give it to Neymon, right?
智障拿算器 他能成b控拿去_
You gave a calculator to a fucking retard he's gonna try turn on the TV with it.
拿好鼓槌L上_去
Now get your stick and get your ass on the stage
我..不行
I... I can't
..不行？
You.. can't?
我上不了_... 我V子]背^
I can't go on stage, I don't know the charts.. by heart.
他逗我呢？
Are you fucking kidding me?
我是... 我... 知道啊
I.. you know this.
我需要V子 那是我X提示物
I need the music, it's my memory, I need visual cues.
-X提示物？  -有@N健康}
-Visual cues?  -It's a medical condition..
健康}？他以樽约菏侵壑郯。拷o我打鼓去!
Medical condition? What are you, fucking Sunjay Gupta? Play the goddamn music!
-我真不行 -我行
-I can't -I can.
背^Whiplash的V子了？
You know Whiplash by heart?
背^了 每拍子都得
Yes sir, every measure.
好吧 最好祈\得蚯宄
Alright. You better fucking hope your memory doesn't fail you
K且比上次排的r候打的好很多
And and you can play a whole lot better than you did last month at the rehearsal
我可不洮F在就卷w回家
Because I do not intend start losing now.
拿好槌子L上_去
Get your stick and get your fucking ass on the stage.
上_！
On stage!
第壹名
And first place
x佛音W院
Shaffer Conservatory
e碰我V子啊
Don't touch my folder man.
e碰我鼓架
Do not touch this kit.
好了_工吧女士
Alright let's get to work ladies.
坦{致锪 今天是核心排 ]rg{教替a
Tanner what are you doing? It's core only today, I don't have time for alternates.
Cherokee 念^_始
Cherokee, from the top.
他是雕像麽 影
Tanner are you a fucking statue? Let's go!
e傻坐著
Get off the stool.
e忘了o嚷翻纷V
Don't forget to turn Neyman's pages.
壹二三四 二二三四
Here we go, one two three four two two three four
妮可：回硪葬峤o我，我^去找？
音肥逢怎麽恿耍
So how's everything going with the Studio Band?
挺好的 我X得他越碓较g我了
Good. I think he likes me more now.
他的看法很重要是吧
And his opinion means a lot to you, doesn't it?
嗯
Yeah
臀叶讼虏
@菜快糊了哎
overcooked.
嚼不勇
can barely chew this
他走
He just left.
安迪 鼓打的怎麽永
So how's drumming going Andy?
嗯特好 我是新核心鼓手了
Yeah it's going really well. I'm the new core drummer...
-f了麽？ -] 怎麽了？
-Did you hear yet?  -No, what happened?
特拉S斯拿了最有r值球T
Travis just got MVP
牛逼啊！
That's fantastic!
_斯汀M模M合了 很快就能拿_德W者W金啦
Dustin is heading up Model UN, soon-to-be-Rhodes-Scholar and who knows what
吉姆是年度教
And Jim, teacher of the year
真的 @壹家子都是天xA啊
I mean, come on, the talent of this table, that is stunning.
哦有安迪 打鼓
And Andy, with your drumming.
行吧安迪?
It's going ok, Andy?
嗯特e 特e好
Yeah I mean it's going really, really well.
我M了x佛W院最好的爵士F
Actually I'm part of Shaffer's top Jazz orchestra
也就是是全最尖的
Which means I'm.. it's the best in the country.
我是核心肥 跟著逢到比
And.. I'm a core member, so I just started playing competitions
前商彀lF自己是全逢最小的
Actually I just found out I'm the youngest person in the entire band.
音繁荣怎麽算A？都是主^感受吧
How do you know wins or not.. a music competition? Isn't it subjective?
不是
No.
音肥医o工作麽？
Does the studio get you a job?
不是那N音肥 “音肥摇敝皇逢的名字
No it's not an actual studio, it's just the name of the ensemble
但@ξ业穆I生涯椭很大
but yeah it's a big step for my career.
嗯值貌诲e就好 我都知道@行很y
Well I'm so glad you figured it out, it's a nasty business I am sure.
哦α s快o我vv@Y拜的球！
Oh are you gonna tell them about your game this week?
什麽叫名副其！
Lived up to your title
我推了93a_
I scored 93 yard touchdown
W校新o啊
School record, school record!
那是三^的球
It's division III.
卡D的校麽 三^的 B二^都]M呢
It's Carleton football, it's not even division II, it's division III
有朋友麽安迪
You got any friends Andy?
-]有  -槭谗幔
-No. -Why's that?
不知道 ]X得朋友有什麽用
I don't know, I just never really saw the use.
那平r都跟l玩啊
Well, who are you going to play with otherwise?
列z和卡尼在W校就是好哥 Π
Lennon and McCartney, they were school friends, am I right?
.斯拿砸查理.帕克之前 查理也]有朋友
Charlie Parker didn't know anybody 'til Joe Jones threw a cymbal at his head.
所以在看砟蔷退愠晒Γ
So that's your idea of success, huh?
我X得成20世o最ゴ蟮囊芳以谡l看矶妓愠晒
I think being the greatest musician of the 20th century is anybody's idea of success.
酗酒吸毒34q就家破人亡在我看砜刹凰愠晒
Dying broke and drunk and full of heroin at the age of 34 is not exactly my idea of success.
我酗酒吸毒 34q就家破人亡 成槿晚餐桌上的}
I'd rather die drunk, broke at 34 and have people at a dinner table talk about me
也不意腰pfM面t光的活到90q 但是]人得我
than live to be rich and sober at 90 and nobody remembered who I was.
但是的朋友得 那才是重c
Ah, but your friends will remember you, that's the point.
我l都不是查理.帕克的朋友 那才是重c
None of us were friends with Charlie Parker. That's the point.
特拉S斯和_斯汀 朋友很多 目艘埠芏
Travis and Dustin? They have plenty of friends and plenty of purpose.
嗯W生主席在合m不^了
I'm sure they'll make great school board presidents someday.
原就是跟@^不去麽？X得比我？
Oh, that's what this is all about? You think you're better than us?
反挺快的啊 模出淼模
You catch on quick. Are you in Model UN?
好了安德 X得卡D橄烨蜿是笑？
I got a reply for you, Andrew. You think Carleton football's a joke?
跟我硪
Come play with us.
4字 下子都M不了NFL
Four words you will never hear from the NFL.
l想吃甜c？
Who wants dessert?
M林肯中心呢？
And from Lincoln Center?
好了今天就到@了
Alright guys, get out of here.
走前e玩了拿新V子
Pick up the new chart by the door on your way out.
今晚9c整排 在那之前好了
Rehearsal 9PM sharp tonight, that's how long you have till then to learn it.
嚷 ^硐
Neyman, just come over here.
看到说墓奏了麽？
See the tempo marking on there?
四分音符速度330
Quarter note equals 330
p倍u[
That is a double-time swing.
就是靠@M淼Π
That's what got you in here right?
是啊
Oh yeah.
和壹 我最近碰到了另外壹小孩
I recently stumbled across another kid
在排室p倍u[
In the practice room working on his double time swing.
所以我想o他C
So I'm gonna give him another shot.
我硗砹耍
Am I late?
淼好
Perfect timing.
M戆煽导{利
Come on in Connelly
zJR吧？
You two know each other right?
嗯嗯 拿K逢
Yeah, yeah, Nassau band.
好啊安德
Hey, what's up Andrew.
嗯 康{利 我嚷Rr核心
Now Connelly I've made Neyman a temporary core.
但是R上就要比了 我只想保C壹切都_到最高水
But with this competition coming up I just wannna make very sure this chart's in the best shape it can be.
是@吧？
Yeah it's the one right here right?
我今天早上o他的V子
I gave Connelly the chart this morning.
F在ozC壹起吧
All you need to do now is to just give both of you a crack at it, alright?
嚷先上吧 念^_始
So Neyman go ahead jump on the kit we'll take it from the top.
好吧
Ok.
e心鼓c 把住奏就好
I don't want you to worry about the hits right now, just tempo.
好
Ok?
e好了？
All set?
奏有c}
Not quite my tempo.
-康{利 -]事我再壹遍
-Connelly? -Ok, I'll take.. from the top.
-我能...  -不用了 康{利戆
-I can do... -No, we'll go with Connelly now.
借用下？
Hey do you mind?
-浜昧耍 -嗯
-Ok? -Yeah
漂亮！
Perfect Connelly
@就是我喜g音肥逢的原因之壹
See this to me is the beauty of Studio Band.
壹替a走M l能想到R上就成新核心了？
You walk in here an alternate, who knows you could be the new core.
靠是逗我呢麽
Oh my god, are you serious?
就@玩意海
That shit?
弗R
Fletcher.
x了哥
Thanks man.
e理弗R 他光打雷不下雨
Don't worry about Fletcher, he's more bark than bite.
-Hey 我能打好@曲子  -F在不是r候
-Hey look, I can play these charts.  -Now's not the time.
-我能打  -我f了不是r候！
-I can play. -I said not now!
要真他想核心 靠本事耆
If you want the fucking part, earn it.
我直f了吧
I'm just gonna lay it out there.
我X得我不再在壹起了
This is why I don't think that we shouldn't be together.
我想了很久
And I thought about it a lot.
接下是@拥模
And this is what's gonna happen, ok?
我壹直追求我所追求的
I'm gonna keep pursuing what I'm pursuing
所以在鼓上花的rg越碓蕉
And because I'm doing that it's gonna take more and more of my time
能陪的rg只越碓缴
And I'm not gonna be able to spend so much time with you.
而我陪的r候MX子全是鼓
And when I do spend time with you, I'll be thinking about drumming.
爵士和纷V
I'll be thinking about Jazz and my charts and all that.
所以t早我
And because of that you're gonna start to resent me.
之後抱怨我v出更多rg砼
And you're gonna tell me to ease up drumming, spend more time with you
因越碓]安全感
because you're not feeling importrant
但我做不到
And I'm not gonna be able to do that.
而且只要壹_始f“少打c鼓”我肯定_始
And I'll just start to resent you for even asking me to stop drumming.
再然後就只能彼此憎毫
And we'll just start to hate each other.
那就不好看了
And it's gonna get very... it's gonna be ugly.
所以fL痛不如短痛 是F在就分手吧
And so... for those reasons, I'd rather just break it off clean.
因槲蚁敫秀
Cuz I wanna be great.
不秀麽？
And you're not?
我想成樽ゴ蟮闹壹
I wanna be one of the greats.
但有我就成不了？
And I'll stop you from doing that?
嗯
Yeah.
知道有我就成不了 就@麽_定@是既定事麽？
You know I'll stop you from doing that. You know that for a fact.
是的
Yes.
即使我缀]怎麽到^
And I barely see you anyway
-嗯  -好不容易到了也劾聿焕淼
-Yeah -And when I did see you you treated me like shit
因槲沂不知道自己要什麽的女孩
because I'm just some girl who doesn't know what she wants
有理想 能成功 我只被人z忘
And you have a path, and you're going to be great, and I'm gonna be forgotten
所以不可能有空陪我
And therefore, you won't be able to give me the time and day
因有更宏h的追求
because you have bigger things to pursue.
跟我想f的壹模壹
That's exactly my point.
他的有病麽？
What the fuck is wrong with you?
f的 我不再在壹起了
You're right, we should not be dating.
不用了xx
I'm ok, thanks.
操！操！
Fuck! Fuck!
操的傻逼！
Fucking piece of shit!
操的！操！
Fuck you! Fuck!
抱歉 新砹鼓手
Sorry we have a new player
瑞安.康{利
Ryan Connelly
不好意思
I'm sorry.
先把菲鞣乓歼吧
Can you just... put your instruments down, for a minute?
壹分
Just listen for a minute.
六年前
Six years ago
我在琴室碰到了壹正在{音A的孩子
I came across a kid in the practice room working on his scales
上大二
He was early second year
汛е希望淼街x佛
and he started in Shaffer with a lot of hope
和壹
Like all you guys.
但事是... 他差c都]能M
but the truth was... He barely squeezed in to begin with and..
那段日子λ很痛苦
He was really struggling.
老都袼 或S真的不是搞音返牧
The faculty were all telling him, maybe this isn't for you.
但他]有看到我所看到的
But they didn't see what I saw.
那瘦小的、@受怕的男孩
That scared, skinny kid,
因橐綦AΣ识咒R自己
cursing himself because he couldn't get the scales right.
我看到的 是他刃o法遏制的_
I saw a drive in him.
於是我把他招M了音肥逢
And I put him in Studio Band.
等到Ir
When he graduated
成了林肯中心的三席手
made him the third trumpet in Lincoln Center.
壹年之後他已是首席了
A year later he was the first.
F在到的就是他
And that's what you're listening to now.
他的名字叫肖恩.P西
His name was Sean Casey.
今天早上我得知 肖恩...
I found out this morning that... Sean
昨天出...
died yesterday.
死了
in a car accident.
我只想...
And I just...
知道 他是壹尤顺錾的肥
want you guys to know he was a beautiful player.
我只是X得知道
I just thought you should know.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好了
Ok.
_工吧
Let's get to work, how about...
Caravan  105小
Caravan, bar 105
壹 二 走
One and two and
康
It's not... not quite right Connelly
嚷吧
I'd like to try Neyman on this.
或SF在是嚷昊睾诵牡r候了
Maybe now is the time for Neyman to earn the part
壹 二 走
One and two and
嗯 是算了吧
No, I guess not.
坦{
Tanner
壹 二 走
One and two and
操的！
Motherfucker!
康{利o我L上去！
Connelly get your ass back on the kit
今晚仨娘炮Y出不了壹能按奏打的咱就不回家了
We'll stay here for as long as it takes till one of faggots can play in time.
壹 二 走
One and two and
看淼猛ㄏ了 嚷
looks like it'll be all night. Neyman.
壹 二 走
One and two and
逼奏不Γ
Not my fucking tempo!
Σ蛔×舜蠹 要@麽等著
Sorry guys, hate to put you through this
如果要上大喝咖啡什麽的
If you need to fucking take a dump or get a coffee whatever
最好F在去
now might be a good time
找不到能按奏打的鼓手前l都e想回家
because we're gonna stay here until I find a drummer who can fucking play in time
先o道歉
I apologize to the musicians.
真的 休息10分 20分 1小r
Seriously, take ten, twenty, a fucking hour
了麽小逼崽子？
You hear me cocksuckers?
最好趁早o我打出完美的400拍
You better start shitting me perfect 400
康{利o我L到鼓架上
Connelly get your fucking ass back on the kit
就只能打@麽快了麽 屁用]有的q太逼
This is really the fastest you can play, you worthless himey fuck?
怪不得不要了 L壹去
No wonder mommy ran out on you. Get off the fucking kit.
有上西^的基佬先生
And here comes Mr. Gay pride of the Upper Western side himself
可惜@不是蒂.米勒的演唱 我不送火焰冰激R和大都u尾酒
Unfortunately this is not a Bette Midler Concert, we'll not be serving Cosmopolitan and Baked Alaska
所以]男朋友的r候有多快就o我打多快
So just play faster than you give fucking hand jobs, will you please?
壹 二 壹 二
One two one two
差的太他h了
Not even fucking close
到mi登隽
Let's go with the Irish mick fucking paddy-cracker now
真他太像小妖精了
You... you actually do look quite a bit like a leprechaun
F在_始我就叫mo吧
I'll start calling you Flannery
L！
Get off!
他看屁呢 地上又]金子
What the fuck you looking... there's not a pot of gold down there
哦{座位啊 逗我？
Oh adjusting the seat, really?!
折v半天}就是座位高度是麽
That's been your fucking problem the whole time? The seat height?
那F在能打好了Π桑
So now you have it right?
走
Go.
扯蛋！傻逼！
Bullshit! Fuck you!
嚷
Neyman.
或S K於是r候上句了 f呢
Maybe, it's time to finally bring this home, what do you say?
o我看看
Show me.
e慢下
Don't slow down!
快c
Pick it up!
再快c！
Faster!
e停！
Keep playing!
嚷
Neyman
昊睾诵牧
You earned the part.
替a o我把鼓架上的血擦
Alternates, you wanna clean the blood off my drum set?
好了 可以_始了
Ok, we can start now.
下午5c到  Dunellen市Y
5pm call tomorrow, in Dunnellen
o自己最少留2小r的rg出l
Give yourself at least two hours to get there from the city this time alright?
得留大巴收
Save your travel receipts.
或者扔了 P我屁事
Or no, I don't give a shit.
Dunellen比日
抱歉打_下 您知道出租在哪瑚幔
Excuse me, do you know where the cabs are?
-得打叫  -他f出租在@接人？
-You have to call the cabs. -I konw, they say the cabs suppose to be right here?
]有啊 得打叫才行 要等很久
No you gotta call them, it'll take forever.
算了租的地方在哪海
Ok how do I get the Hardrove?
快c快c ePT ePT
Come on please, come on, you're still open! You're still open!
快c 快
Come on, come on!
-好? -他跑哪喝チ耍5c就要_始了
-Yeah hello? -Where the fuck are you man? Call time is 5
我知道我知道 R上到了 R上到了
I know, I know, I'm almost there. I'm almost there man. I'm right there.
-有20分就要上_了  -我知道有20分上_
-We're on stage in 20 -I know we're on stage in 20
-弗R匾呀康{利_始嵘砹  -康{利!
-Fletcher got Connelly warming up... -God fucking damnit!
告V那臭婊子我R上就到
You just tell that little fucking redhead I'm gonna be there ok?
操
Fuck
Hey 不好意思硗砹
Hey, Sorry I'm late.
哦H鄣 y得D出rg^砹
Glad you finished on your busy schedule, darling.
我知道 Σ黄 我砹渖霭
I know. Look, I'm sorry, but I'm here man, ready to go.
今天康{利是核心
Connelly's playing the part.
去他的康{利核心
Like fucking hell he's playing my part.
他再o我f壹遍？
What the fuck did you just say to me?
我是核心
It's my part.
核心是我的 我想ol就ol
It's my part, and I decide who to lend it to.
壹般oЧ拈车娜
Usually to somebody that has fucking sticks.
我忘Y了 R上回
I left in the car, I'll be right back
-5分  -已_始嵘砹
-Take me 5 minutes. -I'm warming up the band now.
-我就不能用下瑞安的鼓槌麽.. -嚷 核心不是了
-Look I can use Ryan's sticks -Neyman you lost the fucking part
操怎麽就不是我了 不能@麽郑
No I didn't, look you can't fucking do this to me!
-不能？！ -不能！
-Can't?! -Yeah!
什麽r候到他斫逃我能质谗岵荒质谗崃耍
When did you become a fucking expert on what I can or cannot do?
平胸柴火o
You fucking weepy-willow shit sack?
核心是我淼
I earned that part.
什麽都]赀^ 我操他真是自以槭堑馁v逼
You never earned anything. God you're a self-righteous prick
上核心全是因弄G了V子
The only reason you are a fucking core is because you misplaced folder.
能M音肥逢全是以在拿K的r候
The only reason you're in Studio Band to begin with is because I told you
我就清清楚楚告V我要找的是什麽
exactly what I'd be asking for in Nassau
-我e了麽？ -]
-Am I wrong?  -Yeah
-我能M音肥逢 是因... -就J了不行麽
-I'm in Studio Band, cause I'm the.. -Why don't you just back off?!
L的 老老o我翻纷V去小婊子
Hey you, fuck off Johnny Utah, turn my pages bitch!
Hey 我他想什麽r候L就得L
Hey, I can cut you any fucking time I want.
x不_我
You wouldn't cut me by now.
看啊逼！
Try me you fucking weasel!
5c半 剩整整11分 我的逢就要上_了
At 5.30, that's exactly 11 minutes, my band is on stage.
那之前要是]有е鼓槌回
If your ass is not on that stool with your own fucking sticks in hand
或者他敢o我打e壹拍
Or you make one fucking mistake
e壹拍
One
我立R送回拿Ko人翻V子翻到I或者退W！
I'll drum your ass back to Nassau where you can turn pages untill you graduate or fucking drop off.
等闹x佛L蛋的r候爸看著都比成功
By the time you are done at Shaffer, you're gonna make daddy look like a fucking successful story
懂？
Got it?
或者 康{利做核心 x
Or, we can let Johnny Utah play the part. You choose.
那是我的核心 我上_的
It's my part, I'll be on your stage.
操... 十分！他的娘炮臭基佬
Fuck... you got ten minutes you fucking pathetic pansy-ass fruit-fuck
-o弗R卣f我R上到  -怎麽@麽久啊 要上_了都
-Hey tell Fletcher I'm coming. -What took you so long man, we're moving on stage right now.
我知道 i出了c}
I know I got locked in my car. It's fine, I'm coming.
“200尺後左D”
"Left turn, 200 feet"
_呢？
Are you driving man?
-] -那那是什麽音？
-No -What the hell is that noise?
靠就告V弗R 我他R上到了!
Ok look why don't you just tell Fletcher, that I am coming you motherfucker!
好麽？
Are you ok?
-好麽？ -嗯我的鼓槌...
-Are you ok? -Yeah I gotta get my sticks.
eeexhc
No no no no, stay away from the car.
-我R上打911  -就l街
-I'm calling 911, it's ok. -Just a couple more blocks.
先生，不用...
Sir, you don't have to...
x佛音W院 音肥逢
Shaffer Conservatory, Studio Band.
第三亲帜痪Wwww.disanlou.org最新字幕共享平_
更多字幕P]第三亲帜痪W，xx！
嚷他想什麽呢？
Neyman, what the fuck?
嚷
Neyman
玩完了
You're done.
女士先生 我代表x佛音W院表示歉意
Gentlemen and ladies, I apologize on behalf of Shaffer Conservatory.
我他弄死！
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
e碰我！
Get off me!
Fuck you!
Fuck you Fletcher Fuck you!
操的傻逼！
You fuck... piece of shit!
Fuck you!
什麽r候找到她的
When did you start talking to her?
我是@周系到父H的
Your father got contacted this week.
知道肖恩.P西麽？
Does the name Sean Casey mean anything to you?
知道他的死麽？
Do you know about his death?
上月他在公寓Y上吊自M了
Last month he hung himself in his apartment.
@和我有什麽P系？
What's that have to do with me?
肖恩患有L期焦]抑郁Y
Sean suffered from anxiety and depression.
他母Hf@是在跟了弗R刂後_始的
His mother claimed this started during his time as Fletcher's student.
肖恩家Yl件不是很好 他也不打算提出VA
Now Caseys aren't wealthy, they don't wanna file suit
那...他想要什麽
So... what do they want?
_保不再有W生遭到弗R氐呐按
To make sure that Terrance Fletcher's never allowed to do this to another student
...闹x佛_除...
他什麽都]做
He didn't do anything.
怎麽了？都Y束了好麽
What's wrong with you? It's over ok?
他不再出F在生命中了 槭谗嵋放^他？
He's out of your life, why would you let him get away with what he did to you?
X得他的教W方式是否太^O端？
Would you characterize his conduct as extreme Andrew?
他是否有在精神上蓄意折磨？
Did he ever intentionally inflict emotional distress?
@案子不有公_C
This will not be a public hearing, you know?
弗R赜肋h不知道是f的
Fletcher will never know it was you who spoke up.
槭谗嵋逼我
Why would you do this to me?
真以槲他@诱勰ネ晡鹤俞
Do you think that I would let him put my son through hell
大u大[走人麽？
And just walk away scot-free?
不知道@是我^o法容忍的麽？
Don't you know I would never let that happen?
@世界上]有什麽ξ冶更重要的了
That there is nothing in the world more important to me than you?
不知道麽？
Don't you know that?
安德？
Andrew?
告V我怎麽f吧
Just tell me what to say.
夏
-Hey 我o壁谎Y留了c零食  -我看到了
-Hi, and... I loaded your pantry with Gushers. -I saw that.
xx
Thanks
爵士F... 特邀嘉e：泰斯.弗R
安德
Andrew
Hey
不知道f了]
Don't know if you heard...
我不在x佛了
I'm not in Shaffer any more.
嗯... 我f了
Yeah I did hear that.
o了？
Did you quit?
不是
Not exactly.
有和肖恩壹玫W生家L...
Some parents got a kid from Sean Casey's year I think
f了些P於我的
to say somethings about me.
我以槌了阿奉承意外 大家最多也就f我比^神秘吧
Although why anybody would have anything other than peaches and cream to say about me is a mystery.
很好笑吧
That's a good laugh right?
-不好意思  -e 我懂
-I'm sorry. -No I get it.
我知道我淞瞬簧
I know I've made enemies.
不^我在指]
I'm conducting though
今年的JVC音饭我回去了
They brought back JVC fest this year
^芍б贾I逢去做_霰硌
They got me opening in a couple of weeks with a pro band.
挺好的啊
That's great.
行吧
It's alright.
f 我X得人...
Truth is, I don't think people...
根本不知道我在x佛做的是什麽
understood what it was I was doing at Shaffer.
我不是去指]的
I wasn't there to conduct.
弱智也uu胳膊控制奏
Any fucking moron can wave his arms and keep people in tempo.
我是去逼他突破自己的O限的
I was there to push people beyond what's expected of them
我相信...
I believe that is...
@是^Σ豢苫蛉钡
an absolute necessity.
不然只浪M掉下壹路易.阿姆斯特朗
otherwise we're depriving the world the next Louie Armstrong
下壹查理.帕克
the next Charlie Parker.
我ov^那查理.帕克怎映椴槔.帕克的故事吧
I told that story about how Charlie Parker became Charlie Parker
-.斯朝他X袋上砸了  -就是@
-Jo Jones threw a cymbal at his head. -Exactly.
r帕克年p _克斯吹的很好
Parker was a young kid. Pretty good on the sax.
壹路拼到淘汰
Gets up to play in the cutting session
然後玩砸了
And he fucks it up.
.斯差c]把他X袋削下
And Jones nearly decapitates him for it.
回到後_受M奚落
and he's laughed off-stage
那晚上哭著入睡 但第二天起 他做了什麽？
crie himself to sleep that night, but the next moring, what does he do?
琴
he practices.
琴 是琴 心中只有壹目
and he practices and he practices, with one goal in mind
再也不能被任何人嘲笑
never to be laughed at again.
壹年後他回到舞_上
And a year later he goes back to the Reno.
吹出了有史以碜钏牛逼的奏
And he steps up on that stage and he plays the best motherfucking solo the world has ever heard.
所以想壹下 如果斯只是f
So imagine if Jones just said.
“可以查理”
"Well that's ok Charlie"
“挺好的 不e”
"That was alright, good job."
然後查理回去想
and Charlie thinks to himself
“操 老子吹的不e啊”
"Well, shit, I did a pretty good job."
再就]有後m了
End of story.
]有大B了
No bird.
ξ碚f那直就是悲
That to me is an absolute tragedy.
但是F在大家就只想要@
But that's just what the world wants now.
都{槭谗峋羰⑺
People wonder why Jazz is dying
of吧哥
I tell you man
去看看每家星巴克Y[的爵士］就懂我意思了
Every Starbucks' Jazz album just proved my point, really.
英ZY再]有哪字
There are no two words in English language
比“不e”更害人的了
more harmful than "good job".
那就]有界限了麽？
But is there a line?
比如... 逼的太狠 下壹查理.帕克反而怵H退出了
You know maybe... you go to far, you discourage next Charlie Parker from ever becoming Charlie Parker?
不的 怎麽？
No man, no.
因橄乱查理.帕克永h不怵H
Because the next Charlie Parker would never be discouraged.
嗯
Yeah.
事是
The truth is, Andrew
我]有^自己的查理.帕克
I never really had a Charlie Parker.
但我努力了
But I tried.
我他的是真努力了
I actually fucking tried.
@壹c就已比多等俗叩倪h多了
And that's  more than most people ever do.
而我永h不樽约涸优力^而道歉
and I'll never apologize for how I tried.
嗯 回了
Alright, see you later.
Hey 安德
Hey Andrew
我不知道怎麽想 但是...
Listen I have no idea how you gonna take this, but...
我去JVC的@支逢
the band I'm leading for JVC
鼓手是差口
The drummer's not cutting it.
懂我意思麽？
You understand what I'm saying?
-不懂  -我用的都是音肥逢的曲目
-No. -I'm using the Studio Band playlist.
Caravan Whiplash
我得找把V子吃透的
I need somebody who really knows these charts.
瑞安.康{利呢
What about Ryan Connelly?
他壹直都是我用砑ぐl恿Φ亩已
Ryan Connelly ever was to me is an incentive for you.
坦{？
Tanner?
坦{DWt了
Tanner switched to premed
是怵H了吧
Guess he got discouraged.
周末回去考]考]吧
Hey, take the weekend, think about it.
-好？ -好妮可 是安德
-Hello? -Hey Nicole, it's Andrew.
-好  -好
-Hi -Hey
有壹子...
Been a while since...
]跟聊天了
I talked to you
嗯... 我就是想f...
Look...
真的Σ黄
I'm really sorry
我不是... 那...
about everything, that's not.. not but.. I'm just
真的Σ黄
really sorry.
我其... 我@周末有演出
But anyway I got... I actually have this show this weekend
是叫... JVC 不知道想不想
It's a... JVC thing, I don't know maybe if you wanna go
在卡耐基≡ 演出完可以壹起去吃匹_
it's in Carnegie Hall and.. we.. maybe get some like.. pizza afterwards
抱怨下W校Y那c事... 什麽的
like.. complain about our schools.. again.
那是... JV？
What... is that JV?
不是 是JVC 那... 是爵士...啦
No it's JVC, it's like a.. it's Jazz... thing.
嗯... 我不知道哎
Ugh... I don't know if I can come.
我得下我男朋友
I have to check with my boyfriend.
好吧
Ok
行
Yeah
我他的 但是我X得他... 估爵士]什麽d趣
I'll check, but I don't know that... he's into Jazz, so...
嗯 不是人人都喜g的
Yeah I mean, not for everybody.
好吧 那就到r候吧
Ok, well I guess maybe I'll see you guys there.
好
Ok.
好 拜
Ok, bye.
好了都好了
Alright gangs, listen up.
於那些第壹次⒓JVC的
Now for those of you who are new with this
...除了卡估都是第壹次吧
which looks like might be everybody except Karl
今晚可以改的人生
Tonight can change your life.
底下的^壹
The folks out there make a phone call
就能成{c唱片的s肥
You can be a blue note signee
EMC客
An EMC client
林肯中心核心
A Lincoln Center core
但如果玩砸了
On the other hand, if you drop the ball
就考]Q行吧
you might be looking for a new line of work because
因檫@些人的另壹特c
the other thing about these cats is
是^目不忘
they never forget.
浜昧耍
We all set?
好好玩吧
Alright, let's have fun.
我是傻逼麽
You think I'm fucking stupid?
啊？
What?
我知道是
I know it was you.
xx 女士先生
Thank you ladies and gentlemen
很s幸能JVC做_鲅莩
We're very excited to be here kicking off the JVC festival this year
我是特斯.弗R @些是~s最秀的音芳
I'm Terrance Fletcher, and these are some of the best musicans in New York
也就是全世界最秀的音芳
which means some of the best musicians in the world.
我演奏些之前的常曲目但是首先淼
And we're gonna do some old standard for you but first
是壹首出自蒂姆.西蒙尼的曲子
we're gonna start out with a new tone By Tim Simonec
叫做Upswinging
called Upswinging
致锬兀浚
What the fuck are you doing?!
打啊！
Come on!
嗯 看]@天分
Yeah I guess maybe you don't have it.
]事 回家吧
Come on, let's go home.
质谗幔
What are you doing?
**
等我提示！
I'll cue you in!
Caravan.
三 四
Three Four!
"FUCK YOU!"
我他把眼球挖出.
I'll gouge out your motherfucking eye.
安德 致锬
Andrew what're you doing man?
等我提示
I'll cue you!
中英g/校/rgS 新浪微博：@h球影小笳娴牟皇IN啊